<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advice on crazyc4t&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advice on crazyc4t&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 23:32:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to bounce back from a relapse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bounceback/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 23:32:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bounceback/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello my fellow readers! Am back with a new blogpost, and am going to talk about how to bounce back, when you screw up, and have a bad streak that seems to never end, and you get frustrated about it, how is affecting your life, and that you feel that is really difficult to come back as you were before, and you wish everything was like before, but let me tell you, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution, with much hope and faith in yourself you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can overthinking ruin your mindset</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/dontoverthink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:56:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/dontoverthink/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well first let me welcome you to this new year 2022! I wish you the best for this year and time to rock on and create and achieve what you most want! I welcome you to this new year with this new blog post! I haven&amp;rsquo;t write an advice post in a while so let&amp;rsquo;s get started!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-overthinking&#34;&gt;What is overthinking?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overthinking is just the action to before doing something you think a lot of that action so you can excuse yourself to not do it, If you need to training, but before showering and getting ready you are already thinking &amp;ldquo;My pinky toe hurts a bit I should stay&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; just getting excuses on top of your head to not do something that you don&amp;rsquo;t feel like doing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to comeback and win in life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 23:53:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/comeback/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the definition of the word &lt;strong&gt;comeback&lt;/strong&gt; shall we?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Comeback: a return to a former higher rank, popularity, position, prosperity, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With that being said, a comeback is when you are on the low side of your streak and you make&#xA;the effort to get back where you deserve and were.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is critical in life, you will have a lot of situations that will demotivate you,&#xA;stop your momentum, your rhythm, and make you begin from scratch again,&#xA;and it will be difficult, to not say painful, since from your growth zone you fell back&#xA;to your comfort zone, and then is when you have to get &lt;strong&gt;up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why minimalism is important in your life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/minimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 23:13:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/minimalism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my first (and not last) blogpost talking about life advice and my opinions&#xA;so just buckle up and enjoy the ride!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-minimalism-in-the-first-place&#34;&gt;What is minimalism in the first place?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is really self-explanatory isn&amp;rsquo;t it? Minimalism is just to live with the bare minimum,&#xA;and that goes for everything in life, from your house decorations to your life activities,&#xA;and the concept of minimalism really is to achieve simplicity with essential quality,&#xA;and that means that is perfect, no need for more or less.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
